HAKAN KARAKOCA

JAVA BACKEND DEVELOPER

CONTACT

- **Q** 0538 838 97 35
- **Q** Gebze , Kocaeli
- https://www.linkedin.com/i n/hakankarakoca/

SKILLS

- Java
- Spring Boot
- Oracle

LANGUAGES

• English (Professional Working)

REFERENCE

Levent Özsoy

Anadolu Sigorta - Team Lead

Phone: 0534 224 92 21

Email: levent.ozsoy@medisasaglik.

com.tr



PROFILE

I provided consultancy services to the corporate company in the insurance sector for which I worked as an outsourcer. Technologies and tools I use; Java 7, Java 17, Spring Boot, Hibernate, Oracle, Jira, Bitbucket, Jboss, Javascript, XML



WORK EXPERIENCE

Medisa

Java Backend Developer

APRIL 2024 - PRESENT

• I work as a Java Backend Developer at Medisa, a company operating in the insurance sector. I provide development of web services using Java 17, Spring Boot and Oracle technologies, as well as bug maintenance and live environment support.

JFORCE

OCTOBER 2021 - PRESENT

Java Backend Developer

- at @Medisa Java Backend Developer (2024 Present)
- at @Anadolu Sigorta Java Backend Developer (2021 2024)

Anadolu Sigorta

OCTOBER 2021-MARCH - 2024

Java Backend Developer

- I work as a Java Backend Developer in the newly established Collection Team at Anadolu Sigorta. During the web applications development process, I produce scalable and efficient solutions by effectively using Java 7 and IDIT framework.
- Technologies:
- · Java 7 · Oracle · EJB · JSP · Hibernate · JPA · JavaScript · XML
- · Agile Metotları · IDIT framework · JIRA · Bitbucket · Git · Maven · Jhoss



EDUCATION

Sakarya Üniversitesi

2013 - 2019

Bachelor degree, Computer Engineering

5